navahang.com 2019-12-05

# Navahang.com - Privacy Policy

Last updated: May 28, 2018  
This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference into the Navahang LLC End User License Agreement and Terms of Service located at https://www.navahang.com/privacy/ (“ **EULA** ”). The terms “ **Navahang,** ” “ **we,** ” “ **us,** ” and “ **our** ” include NAVAHANG, LLC and its affiliates and/or subsidiaries. All other terms not defined in this Privacy Policy will have the meanings set forth in the EULA.

This Privacy Policy explains how NAVAHANG may collect, use, process, disclose and safeguard information we obtain through the Service, including our website (currently at [www.NAVAHANG.com](https://tunein.com/)) and our mobile applications, and in connection with our partner and vendor relationships. It also tells you about your rights and choices with respect to your Personal Information, and how you can contact us if you have any questions or concerns.

**HOW NAVAHANG COLLECTS YOUR INFORMATION**

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, “ **Personal Information** ” means any information relating to an identified or identifiable individual. We obtain Personal Information relating to you from various sources as described below.

Where applicable, we indicate whether and why you must provide us with your Personal Information, as well as the consequences of failing to do so. If you do not provide Personal Information when requested, you may not be able to benefit from our Service if that information is necessary to provide you with the Service or if we are legally required to collect it.

  * **Personal Information Obtained from Third Parties**

**Social Sign-on.**  We collect information from social media services when you use your credentials for these services to log into the Service. For example, when you log in with your Facebook credentials, we collect the information you have authorized Facebook to share with us, such as your name, email address, gender, date of birth, and profile picture. We may also obtain other non-public information with your permission.

**Other Third Parties.**  We may collect information about you from other third parties, such as other users or our marketing partners. For example, we may receive information about you when another user allows us to upload your contact information to the Service. We may combine this information with the other information we collect about you.

  * **Personal Information Collected From your Device via Automated Means**

**Using the Service.**  When you use the Service, we collect information about your activities, such as the stations, artists or channels that you listen to, the User profiles that you view, your searches for friends or stations and your other actions and interactions with other Users or content on the Service, the stations, content and people that you follow (“ **Follow Lists** ”), your comments, any content that you post on the Service, and any other information resulting from your use of the Service that is publicly accessible by other Users (“ **Public Information** ”).

**Your Contacts.**  If you give us permission to import to the Service the contacts from any email account associated with your account, then we may collect information about your contacts. We may also collect your contacts if you share information or content with them from the Service or invite them to use the Service.

**Location Information.**  With your consent, we may obtain information about your physical location at regular intervals when you use the Service, such as by use of geolocation features in the device(s) through which you access the Service. In addition, we may infer your location from other information we collect (for example, your IP address indicates the general geographic region from which you are connecting to the Internet). We use location information to comply with radio stations’ content licenses (which are location-specific), and to provide you with features, notifications, advertising, or other content that is influenced by your location (such as showing you your local radio station).

**Device Information.**  We receive information from Users’ devices through which a User accesses the Service, such as IP address, web browser type, mobile operating system version, and unique device identifiers.

**Cookies and Related Technologies.**  When you visit the Service, we and our third party service providers receive and record information from your browser and from cookies and similar technologies. Cookies are small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Service. Please review your web browser’s “Help” file to learn the proper way to modify your cookie settings. Please note that if you delete, or choose not to accept, cookies from the Service, you may not be able to utilize the features of the Service to their fullest potential.

Third parties that advertise goods or services on the Service (collectively, “ **Advertisers** ”) may also use cookies or other technologies to track your use of the Service. Advertisers also may use cookies to track your online activities across websites over time to provide interest-based advertising. Some of our Advertisers are members of the [Network Advertising Initiative](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) or the [Digital Advertising Alliance](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/). Please visit these organizations’ opt-out pages to learn about how you may opt out of receiving web-based personalized ads from member companies. Please visit your device’s settings or install the AppChoices app to learn more about how you may opt out of receiving personalized ads in mobile apps.

One of the third party services that we use to track your activity on the Service is Google Analytics. If you do not want Google Analytics to collect and use information about your use of the website, then you can install an opt-out in your web browser (<https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>). You also may opt-out from Google Analytics for Display Advertising or the Google Display Network by using Google’s Ads Settings located at [www.google.com/settings/ads](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).

**HOW NAVAHANG USES YOUR INFORMATION**

**Internal and Service-Related Usage.**  We use Personal Information for internal and Service-related purposes, including to operate, provide, and maintain the Service.

**Analytics and Improving the Service.**  We and our service providers use Personal information that we collect on the Service, such as your location and your activities on the Service, to monitor and analyze usage of the Service and to improve and enhance the Service.

**Communications.**  We may send emails to an email address you provide to us (i) for customer-service or technical-support purposes, or (ii) to send you (a) information about topics or content that we think may interest you, or (b) updates about the latest developments or features on the Service. We also may send push notifications to your device and a newsletter to the email address you provide to us in the event that you subscribe to receive the newsletter.

**Advertising.**  We and our advertising partners may use your Personal Information, including your location and your activities on the Service to facilitate the delivery of advertisements.

**Tailored Content.**  We may use your Personal Information to provide you with personalized services, content, offers and recommendations. For example, we may analyze your listening history to recommend similar content that we think would be of particular interest to you, send you tailored recommendations based on your location or send you personalized marketing communications based on Personal Information we have collected about you.

**Aggregate Data.**  We may de-identify and aggregate information collected through the Service for statistical analysis and other lawful purpose.

**Partners and Vendors.**  We use information collected from our business partners and vendors to manage those relationships.

**Job Applications.**  If you apply for a job at NAVAHANG, we may process your Personal Information to evaluate your application.

**Legal.**  We may use your Personal Information to enforce our [End User License Agreement and Terms of Service](https://www.navahang.com/terms/), to defend our legal rights, to comply with our legal obligations and internal policies.

If you are located in the European Economic Area (“ **EEA** ”):

  * We only process your Personal Information based on a valid legal ground, including when you have consented to the use of your Personal Information, for example, to provide you with tailored advertising.
  * We need your Personal Information to provide you with the Services, including for account registration, to respond to your inquiries or, if you are a broadcaster, to manage the directory listing and for support.
  * We have a legal obligation to use your Personal Information, such as the obligation to protect intellectual property rights and restrict content available on the Service based on your location.
  * We or a third party have a legitimate interest in using your Personal Information. In particular, we have a legitimate interest in using your Personal Information to personalize our Service and provide you with tailored content, conduct business analytics and otherwise improve the safety, security, and performance of our Service. We only rely on our or a third party’s legitimate interests to process your Personal Information when these interests are not overridden by your rights and interests.

**HOW NAVAHANG MAY DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION**

**Vendors and Service Providers.**  We may share any Personal Information we receive with vendors and service providers retained in connection with the provision of the Service. For example, we may use service providers to measure app usage and user engagement (e.g., Google Analytics for Firebase), serve advertising on our Services (e.g., MoPub, Inc.) or provide DDoS mitigation services (e.g., Cloudflare, Inc.).

**Advertising Partners.**  We may share your Personal Information with our third party advertising partners to provide ads that we think may interest you. For more information about our advertising and marketing practices and those of the third party advertising partners, please see the  **Cookies and Related Technologies**  section above.

**Nonaffiliated Companies.**  We do not rent, sell, or share Personal Information (as defined by California Civil Code §1798.83) about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies for their direct marketing purposes, unless we have your permission. If we receive your permission, nonaffiliated companies may use your Personal Information to send you offers or other information that you may find of interest.

**Social Networking and Other Websites.**  The Service may allow you to share Personal Information with social networking services, such as Facebook. We do not share your Personal Information with them unless you direct the Service to share it. Their use of your Personal Information is governed by their privacy policies, and you may be able to modify your privacy settings on their services.

**Search Engines.**  Your Public Information may also be accessible through search engines, such as Google or Yahoo, just like with many common social media services.

**Other Third Parties.**  We may also share Personal Information about you with other third parties in the following circumstances:

  * **With Your Consent.**  We may disclose your Personal Information with your permission. We may seek your permission in various ways. For example, we may present you with an “opt-in” prompt when you register to use the Service or access certain content
  * **To Comply with Legal Obligations.**  We may access, preserve, and disclose your Personal Information or other account information if we believe doing so is required or appropriate to (i) comply with laws, law enforcement requests, and legal process, such as a court order or subpoena; (ii) respond to your requests; or (iii) protect your, our or others’ rights, property, or safety.
  * **In case of Merger, Sale, or Other Asset Transfers.**  If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, financing due diligence, reorganization, bankruptcy or liquidation where the business will not continue as a going concern, receivership, sale of NAVAHANG assets, or transition of the Service to another provider, then your information may be sold or transferred as part of such a transaction as permitted by law and/or contract. The use of your information following any of these events should be governed by the provisions of this Privacy Policy in effect at the time the applicable information was collected.

**SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards that are intended to appropriately protect Personal Information against accidental or unlawful destruction, accidental loss, unauthorized alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access, misuse, and any other unlawful form of processing of the Personal Information in our possession. Unfortunately, the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any Personal Information you provide to us.

**DATA RETENTION**

We take measures to delete your Personal Information or keep it in a form that does not permit identifying you when this information is no longer necessary for the purposes for which we process it, unless we are required by law to keep this information for a longer period. When determining the retention period, we take into account various criteria, such as the type of products and services requested by or provided to you, the nature and length of our relationship with you, possible re-enrolment with our products or services, the impact on the services we provide to you if we delete some information from or about you and mandatory retention periods provided by law and the statute of limitations.

**THIRD PARTY PRIVACY PRACTICES**

This Privacy Policy applies only to the processing of your Personal Information by NAVAHANG. The Service may contain links to third party sites, such as CNN and ESPN (“ **Third Party Sites** ”). The policies and procedures described in this Privacy Policy do not apply to Third Party Sites. The links from the Service to any Third Party Sites do not imply that we endorse or have reviewed the Third Party Sites.

**CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**

We do not knowingly collect, maintain, or use personal information, as defined by the Federal Trade Commission’s Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Rule, from children under 13 years of age, and no part of the Service is directed to children under the age of 13. If you are located in the EEA, we do not knowingly collect, maintain, or use Personal Information from children under 16 years of age, and no part of the Service is directed to children under the age of 16. If you learn that your child has provided us with Personal Information without your consent, then you may alert us at info@NAVAHANG.com. If we learn that we have collected any Personal Information from children under 13 (or 16 in the EEA), then we will promptly take steps to delete such information and terminate the child’s account.

**DATA TRANSFERS**

If you are visiting the Service from regions with laws governing data collection and use, then please note that you are agreeing to the transfer of your Personal Information to the United States and processing globally. By providing your Personal Information to the Service, you consent to any transfer and processing in accordance with this Policy.

If you are located in the EEA, we comply with EU data protection law when transferring your Personal Information outside of the EEA. In particular, we may transfer your Personal Information to non-EEA countries, including to the United States where we are headquartered. To protect Personal Information transferred from the EEA or Switzerland to the United States. We have certified to the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield frameworks.

**YOUR DATA PROTECTION RIGHTS (EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREA).**

If you are located in the EEA or Switzerland, you may have the following additional rights to:

  * Request access to and receive information about the Personal Information we maintain about you, to update and correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information, restrict or to object to the processing of your Personal Information, have the information anonymized or deleted, as appropriate, or exercise your right to data portability to easily transfer your Personal Information to another company. In addition, you may also have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, including in your country of residence, place of work or where an incident took place.
  * Withdraw any consent you previously provided to us regarding the processing of your Personal Information, at any time and free of charge. We will apply your preferences going forward and this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before your consent withdrawal.

Those rights may be limited in some circumstances by local law requirements. You may exercise these rights by using the How to Contact Us below.

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY AND PRACTICES**

**Posting of Revised Privacy Policy.**  We will post any adjustments to the Privacy Policy on this web page, and the revised version will be effective when it is posted. If you are concerned about how your information is used, then bookmark this page and read this Privacy Policy periodically.

**New Uses of Information.**  From time to time, we may desire to use or disclose Personal Information for uses not previously disclosed in our Privacy Policy. If our practices change regarding previously collected information in a way that would be materially less restrictive than stated in the version of this Privacy Policy in effect at the time we collected the information, then we will make reasonable efforts to provide notice and obtain consent prior to any such uses as may be required by law.

**Contact Information.**  If you have any questions, would like to exercise your rights or share suggestions for improving the Privacy Policy or the Service, please feel free to [contact us](https://www.navahang.com/contact-us/)
